{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20ancient%20civilization%20is%20credited%20with%20the%20invention%20of%20writing%20using%20hieroglyphics%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Ancient%20Egypt",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ancient%20Greece",
        "Ancient%20China",
        "Mesopotamia"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20was%20the%20first%20emperor%20of%20ancient%20Rome%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Augustus",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Julius%20Caesar",
        "Nero",
        "Constantine"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "The%20French%20Revolution%20began%20in%20which%20year%3F",
      "correct_answer": "1789",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1776",
        "1804",
        "1812"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20country%20was%20the%20first%20to%20circumnavigate%20the%20globe%20and%20reach%20the%20Philippines%20in%201521%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Spain",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Portugal",
        "England",
        "France"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20was%20the%20leader%20of%20the%20Soviet%20Union%20during%20the%20Cuban%20Missile%20Crisis%20in%201962%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Nikita%20Khrushchev",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Joseph%20Stalin",
        "Vladimir%20Putin",
        "Mikhail%20Gorbachev"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20event%20is%20considered%20the%20start%20of%20World%20War%20I%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Assassination%20of%20Archduke%20Ferdinand%20of%20Austria",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Battle%20of%20the%20Somme",
        "Treaty%20of%20Versailles",
        "Invasion%20of%20Poland"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20ancient%20civilization%20is%20known%20for%20constructing%20the%20Great%20Wall%20of%20China%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Qin%20Dynasty",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ming%20Dynasty",
        "Han%20Dynasty",
        "Tang%20Dynasty"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "The%20Treaty%20of%20Versailles%20was%20signed%20in%20which%20year%3F",
      "correct_answer": "1919",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1914",
        "1924",
        "1920"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20was%20the%20first%20female%20Prime%20Minister%20of%20the%20United%20Kingdom%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Margaret%20Thatcher",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Queen%20Elizabeth%20II",
        "Theresa%20May",
        "Indira%20Gandhi"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "The%20Berlin%20Wall%20fell%20in%20which%20year%3F",
      "correct_answer": "1989",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1991",
        "1987",
        "1990"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
